纸牌屋
第四季  第五集
两个月前  卢卡斯·古德温被从印第安纳州
Lucas Goodwin was released from a federal detention center
卢卡斯·古德温的家
泰瑞豪特一家联邦监狱释放
in Terre Haute, Indiana, two months ago.
联调局调查员搜查了他在俄亥俄州代顿的
FBI investigators searched his witness protection residence
-证人保护计划住处  -他怎么会被释放
- in Dayton, Ohio... - Why was he even out of jail?
他在一起调查中协助了司法部
He helped the DOJ with an ongoing investigation.
你怎么会不知道
How did you not know that?
证人保护计划  出于安全考虑高度保密
WITSEC. Only need-to-know for security reasons.
我们今天在他家发现了这个
We found this today at his house.
大概是遗书吧
A suicide note, I guess.
...外遇...佐伊·巴恩斯
这不能被公开
This can't go public.
我们还没对媒体透露半句
We haven't told the press anything.
但这是证据
But this is evidence.
一旦报告出来
Once the report comes out...
道格·斯坦普  幕僚长
瑞秋·波斯纳
把这个电邮给我
Email this to me.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood?
现在凌晨两点了  您要回家吗
It's two o'clock in the morning. Would you like to go home?
嗯  我待会儿就出去
Oh, yes, I'll be out in a moment.
是  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
他的肝再生速度不够快
His liver is just not regenerating fast enough.
那具体是什么意思
What does that mean, exactly?
他需要移植  否则会死
He needs a transplant, or he'll die.
-什么时候  -几天之内
- How soon? - Days.
我们将他列为了1号情况
We've made him Status 1.
我们相信能为他找到合适的肝脏
I'm optimistic we'll find him a suitable liver.
接受者名单是机密
The recipient list is classified.
只有您两位政府成员
You're the only two members of the administration
知情
who've been briefed.
第一夫人知道了吗
Is the First Lady aware?
是的  我今天下午告诉她了
Yes, I informed her this afternoon.
我可以进来吗
May I?
请吧
Please.
我知道很晚了  但他们说你没睡
I know it's late, but they said you were up, so...
我知道  我就是一天都没吃东西了
No, I know. I just hadn't eaten all day.
你也是吧
I'm sure you haven't.
-来点沙拉吗  -好啊  谢谢
- Would you like some salad? - Sure. Thank you.
弗兰克的事  真是可怕
It's scary, about Frank.
弗兰西斯是个斗士
Well, Francis is a fighter.
真希望我能问他的建议
I wish I could ask his advice.
我明早要跟佩特罗夫通电话了
I have my call with Petrov in the morning.
我对计划颇为了解  这点我有自信
I feel good about my understanding of the plan.
我担心的是他在电话里威胁我
My concern is him railroading me on the call.
你希望我跟你一起打吗
Well, would you like me to be on it?
多个人听听
An extra set of ears.
我不知道凯茜会有什么想法
I don't... I don't know how Cathy would feel about that.
不非得让她知道啊
Well, she doesn't need to know.
我可以在这里听
I could just listen from up here.
如果你有麻烦  或许我可以发点建议过去
And maybe I could type a note if you get into trouble.
...对总统的恢复闭口不言
...tight-lipped on the president's recovery.
到目前  据报他情况稳定
As of now, he's reported to be in stable condition.
尚无媒体被允许进入医院
No press has been allowed into the hospital.
共和党候选人威尔·康威
Republican presidential hopeful Will Conway
今早在亚利桑那州一场集会上提到了总统
spoke of the president at a rally in Arizona this morning.
我经常批评安德伍德总统
I've criticized President Underwood often.
但此刻  他是我们的总统
But right now, he's our president...
明天来吧  我们没油了
Come back tomorrow. We're all out.
两党要团结一致
...and we have to pull together, both sides of the aisle...
我们今天没油了
We're all out for today.
抱歉  明天再来吧
Sorry, come back tomorrow.
-没油了  没油了  -不是吧
- We're all out, guys. We're all out. - Are you serious?
明天再来吧  我们今天没油了  先生
Come back tomorrow. We're all out for today, sir.
真扯
Bullshit!
我能从你这儿吸几加仑吗
Can I siphon a couple of gallons from you?
五十块  我没油了已经
Fifty bucks. I'm running on fumes.
我还得送孩子上学  送老公上班
I gotta get my kids to school, and my husband to work--
八十块  两加仑
Eighty bucks, two gallons.
抱歉  帮不了你  抱歉
Sorry, I can't help you. Sorry.
普通汽油  高级汽油  精品汽油  全部现金支付
杰·夏普  你在华府吗  这边加班加点呢
总统  油价危机
如果能休息一下就太好了
雷·丹顿  佛罗里达呢  看爸妈来了
或许也好  诱惑最讨厌了
我想你...
接通了吗
The line's open?
莫斯科就等您了  先生
Moscow is ready when you are, sir.
放在这里就好
You can set it up here.
我的小抄
My Cliff Notes.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
说话别含糊其辞
自信  你有筹码的
总统先生  您已与佩特罗夫总统接通
Mr. President, you're on with President Petrov.
总统先生
Mr. President.
俄国举国上下都在为总统的康复祈祷
All of Russia is praying for the president's recovery.
希望代我转达对安德伍德夫人的问候
I hope you will extend my warm thoughts to Mrs. Underwood.
我会的
I certainly will.
你真是勇敢
You're a brave man
在如此艰难的时刻接手
to take over during such difficult times.
我只想确保
I just want to make sure
我们找到可行方案解决这场油价...
we find a manageable resolution to this oil--
我读过你写的一些书  总统先生
I've read some of your books, Mr. President.
我刚读完《学会学习》
I just finished Learning to Learn.
很不错
It was good.
谢谢
Thank you.
有一章关于想象的令我很感兴趣
There was a chapter on visualization that really interested me.
是的  是学生可用的工具  帮助他们
Yes, it's a... A tool for students. It helps them--
我想请你想象一下
I would like you to visualize something.
你站在苔原上
Now, you're standing in the tundra.
大风  暴雪
Um, wind, snow...
机器在钻透冰层
machines drilling through the ice,
长长的管线延伸至远处的地平线  你能想象吗
long pipelines stretching to the horizon. Do you see?
如果你想谈西伯利亚  我很乐意...
If you want to talk about Siberia, I'm more than happy to--
不不  你不是在想象
No, no, no. You're not visualizing,
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President.
闭上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
配合他  让他说
好吧  闭上了
All right. They're closed.
很好  那么
Good. Now...
想象工人
picture the men
在钻井和管线上工作
working those drills and pipelines.
他们什么样
What do they look like?
大棉衣  戴手套  穿着靴子
Um, heavy coats, gloves, boots.
他们是  中国人吗
Are they... Chinese?
瞧  当我想象的时候
You see, when I picture this,
我看不到中国人
I don't see Chinese.
我同意  中国的控制权越少越好
I agree with you. The less control the Chinese have, the better.
那你为什么把米尔金送去中国
Then why did you send Milkin to China?
你不肯跟我们谈判
You weren't negotiating with us.
我们觉得或许他们的运气会更好
We thought they might have more luck.
他们的要求会让我们陷入比之前更糟的境地
Their demands would leave us worse off than we were before.
我可以让国际货币基金组织拿出一半的救市资金
I can get the IMF to provide half the bailout.
这可以制衡中国对开采权的要求
This would counteract the Chinese demands for drilling rights--
你是想挑拨我们
You are playing us off each other.
总统先生
Mr. President--
我觉得  你是自不量力了  布莱斯先生
I think you're in over your head, Mr. Blythe.
容我解释一下
If you would just give me a chance to elaborate--
凭什么让你解释
Why give you a chance?
你对俄国  对中国有什么了解
What do you know about Russia? About China?
我已经听过了...
I've been briefed on--
抱歉  但是
Forgive me, but, uh...
我不愿跟
I don't feel comfortable
总统以外的人进行谈判
negotiating with anyone other than the president.
等他康复  或许我们可以谈谈
When he recovers, perhaps he and I can speak.
告诉他总统可能会死
我们完事了吗
So, are we finished?
告诉他总统可能会死
总统情况很糟
The president's in very bad shape.
先生
Sir...
多严重
How serious is it?
他得习惯跟你商议
他需要肝脏移植
He needs a liver transplant.
我不知道
I wasn't aware that...
你最好习惯跟我磋商
You better get used to negotiating with me.
如果总统死了  那就是你和我
If the president dies, it's you and I...
否则没得可谈
or nothing at all.
抱歉  总统先生
My apologies, Mr. President.
我无意侮辱你
I didn't intend to insult you.
我们继续协商  我只求这个
Let's keep a dialogue open. That's all I'm asking.
我想给你一份应对中方要求的
I'd like the opportunity to present you with a detailed proposal
具体提议
countering the Chinese demands.
我会让国务卿杜兰特跟你的外交部长接洽
I'll have Secretary Durant work with your foreign minister,
然后我们再谈
and then we'll take it from there.
这样可以吗
Are you open to that?
当然
Of course.
我很期待看到你的提议
I look forward to reviewing your proposal.
谢谢  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
先生  这消息我们还不希望被透露出去
Sir, we didn't want that to get out to the press yet.
美国人民反正也该知道
The American people deserve to know, anyway.
先生  俄国人是见软就欺
Sir, the Russians don't respond well to weakness.
现在他们知道总统...
Now that they know that the president--
你听到他说愿意协商了
You heard him say he's open to negotiation.
我认为这是进展
I'd say that's progress.
四天了  还没有吗
Four days and still nothing?
没有记者招待会  没有通报
No press conference, no briefing.
我们得让他们
We have to let them conduct
按自己的步调进行调查
their investigation on their own terms.
感觉好像我们被蒙在鼓里
Feels like we're being shut out.
不仅仅是联调局
This isn't just the bureau.
他们还得跟国土安全部协调
They have to coordinate with Homeland
-确保敏感...  -扯淡
- and make sure nothing sensitive-- - That's bullshit.
古德温有什么情况你不希望我们知道
There's something about Goodwin that you don't want us to know.
不对
Wrong.
我跟你一样想知道他这么做的动机
I wanna know why he did this just as much as you do...
但我们得让联调局做他们的工作
But we've gotta let the FBI do its job.
跟我去看他时是同一个论调
Same theory as when I visited him.
那是他达成认罪协议之前  是吗
And that was before he struck the plea, correct?
我鼓励他认罪的
I encouraged him to plead guilty.
他的宣称毫无依据
His claims were unsubstantiated.
跟我们说说你去见古德温之前
Tell us about your meeting with the president
跟总统的见面
prior to that meeting with Goodwin.
卢卡斯拜托我调查  我就调查了
Lucas asked me to investigate. I did.
因此采访了安德伍德
That involved an interview with Underwood.
你还留着笔记吗
You still have your notes?
没有搜查令我不会交出笔记
No notes without a warrant.
媒体  没日没夜地打
The press. Calling non-stop.
我们建议调查期间你不要跟任何人...
We suggest you don't speak to anyone while we're still--
别担心  我完全不想被扯进来
Don't worry. I don't have any interest in getting dragged into this.
我去把笔记找出来
Let me go dig up those notes.
布莱斯  他告诉佩特罗夫总统需要移植
Blythe... He told Petrov the president needs a transplant.
他为什么要那么做
Why would he do that?
佩特罗夫把他气到了
Petrov got under his skin.
这就是为什么我们本该按你丈夫的计划来
This is why we should've carried out your husband's plan.
我们给了莫斯科太多操作的空间
We're giving Moscow too much room to maneuver--
我们别谈论无法改变的事了  道格
Let's not debate what we can't change, Doug.
如果莫斯科知道了  我们就得通知媒体
If Moscow knows, we'll have to notify the press.
我们明天就说
We're doing that tomorrow.
由萨克逊医生来做通告
Dr. Saxon will do the briefing.
不  我来吧
No, I'll do it.
还是由第一夫人来说的好
It's better coming from the First Lady.
我同意
I agree.
这事我们也得应对一下
We need to address this, too.
联调局在古德温家找到了他的遗书
The FBI found Goodwin's notes in his house.
可以给处理掉吗
Can we make them disappear?
不行  已经被收为证据了
No, it's already been catalogued.
我们得先一步采取行动控制舆论
We need to get out ahead of it and control the story.
好吧  给我弄一份目前为止的调查报告
All right. Get me a copy and report on the investigation so far.
我想见他
I wanna see him.
总统
The president.
特勤局不许我进去
The Secret Service still won't let me.
请允许斯坦普先生见我丈夫
I'd like Mr. Stamper to have access to my husband, please.
我们有严格命令  夫人  只有您
We have strict orders, ma'am. Only you and--
需要我亲自打给副总统吗
Would you like me to call the vice president myself?
道格拉斯  这位年轻人会送你进去
Douglas, this young man will escort you to his room.
谢谢
Thank you.
-几点了  -7点刚过
- What time is it? - It's a little past 7:00.
先生  先生  是道格
Sir? Sir, it's Doug.
虽然他睁开了眼
Just because his eyes are open
但不代表他的意识完全清醒了
doesn't mean he's fully conscious.
肝功能不足
Insufficient liver function.
他的大脑泡在一堆未处理的氨中
His brain is swimming in a pool of unprocessed ammonia.
如果他能看到什么  大概也是严重的幻觉
If he's seeing anything, it's probably severe hallucinations.
他多久能得到肝脏
How long until he has a liver?
可能得要几小时  可能要几天
Could be hours. Could be days.
他是名单上第三位
He's number three on the list.
第三名
Number three?
名单按序排序
It's prioritized in terms of need
他是1号情况的第一位
and who was listed first as a Status 1.
他是美国总统啊
He's the President of the United States.
这是法律
It's the law.
纳·格林  我们知道是谁泄露了照片
赛斯·格雷森
道·斯坦普  我上车打给你
司法部长要辞职
The attorney general is resigning.
把这条加入今天下午的新闻发布稿中
Add that to the press release for this afternoon.
-是她的决定还是副总统  -我的决定
- Uh, her decision or the vice president's? - My decision.
古德温的证人保护计划是司法部的责任
Goodwin's WITSEC was a DOJ responsibility.
我们得找个替罪羊
We needed a head to roll.
先是她  然后你
First hers... then yours.
你明天辞职
You'll resign tomorrow.
道格  我知道你现在压力很大  但是
Doug, I know you're under a lot of pressure, but--
是你发了那张南军士兵照片
You sent the photo of the rebel soldier.
不是的
That's not true.
私人手机  没在这里发
Personal phone, off the premises.
可能是有人黑了我的账户什么的
You know, maybe somebody hacked my account or something--
你真要再这么对我撒谎吗
Are you really gonna keep lying to me?
我可以叫人逮捕你
I could have you arrested.
但我宁可你低调离去
But I'd rather you go quietly.
我知道些事  道格
I know things, Doug.
你证明不了什么
Nothing you can prove.
再威胁我啊
Now, threaten me again.
中国如果不加入  提议就不能成型
There's no proposal without China's involvement.
凯茜试了
Now, Cathy's tried,
但她跟他们的关系不是特别好
but she doesn't have the best relationship with them.
或许她需要帮助
Maybe she needs some help.
帮助  怎么说
Help? How?
你介意我抽烟吗
Do you mind if I smoke?
当然不
Of course not.
我十年前戒了
I quit about ten years ago.
玛乔莉逼我的
Marjory forced me to.
还是那么好闻
Ah, still smells delicious.
玛乔莉死时什么样
What was it like when Marjory died?
那是...
Oh, well, it was, um...
抱歉  如果你不愿意我们不用谈这个
I'm sorry. We don't have to talk about it if you don't want.
不  没事
No, it's fine.
我们当时已经数月没有真正聊过了
We hadn't had a real conversation in... in months.
她的神智已经不清楚了
Her mind was gone.
她最终死时
When she finally died,
感觉好像断了根肋骨
it felt like a limb had been hacked off.
我...痛不欲生
I felt... devastated.
但也如释重负
But I also felt relieved.
我对我母亲的感觉就是这样
That's what I feel about my mother.
我不...我都没想起来
Oh, I hadn't-- It hadn't even occurred to me.
除了弗兰克  你母亲也病了
You have Frank and your mother.
父亲去世时  我几乎崩溃了
When my father died, it destroyed me,
但想到我母亲时  我毫无感觉
but when I think about Mother, I feel nothing.
-你们不亲近吗  -不
- You two aren't close? - No.
我对弗兰西斯也是这种感觉
And I feel the same about Francis.
毫无感觉
Nothing.
我知道这听起来很可怕
I know that must sound awful.
这很难接受
It's a lot to process.
这没有正误之分
There's no right way or wrong way.
-等下  慢着  -不
- Wait, hold on. - No.
玛乔莉不会同意的
Marjory wouldn't approve.
刚刚说到哪了
We got sidetracked.
对  中国
Yes. China.
我有个主意  如果你相信我能做好的话
I have an idea, if you can trust me to handle it.
我赌上命相信你  克莱尔
I'd trust you with my goddamn life, Claire.
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
我来拿  谢谢
I got it. Ah, merci.
莉安
LeAnn.
找你可真难
You are a tough guy to track down.
-你来干什么  -你要赶飞机
- What are you doing here? - You have a plane to catch.
第一夫人需要你的帮助
The First Lady needs your help.
我不想和他们有任何瓜葛
I don't want to have anything to do with them.
无论你对总统的看法如何
Whatever you think of the president,
你对祖国依然负有责任
you still have a duty to your country.
就算他在我离开白宫的那天去世
Even if he dies, the day I walked out the White House,
我也向自己承诺过不会回去
I promised myself I wasn't going back.
你连我们的计划都不知道
You don't even know what we have in mind.
无所谓  我不去
It doesn't matter. I'm not going.
我想请你离开
I'd like you to leave.
这是基本情况的材料
Here's your briefing materials.
你没听见我说吗
You're not hearing me.
你真应该看一眼
You should really take a look.
她的竞选会完蛋的
Her campaign would be over.
而且你父母会怎么想
And what would your parents think?
看上去就像你要利用他受伤...
It looks like you're taking advantage of the fact that he's--
康威仍在进行竞选活动
Conway is still campaigning.
他是共和党人
He's a Republican
而且他已经得到了提名
and he's already wrapped up his nomination.
和我们不一样
Apples and oranges.
如果我们什么都不做
We are gonna lose,
陪着一个不省人事的人干坐着  就会输
if we sit still, to a guy who's unconscious.
希瑟说得对  安德伍德在大赚同情分
Heather's right. Underwood's scoring major sympathy points.
在接下来的七个州里  他在六个州领先
He's ahead in six of the next seven states.
我们得继续施压
We need to keep the pressure up.
俄国  油价
Russia, gas prices...
攻击一位正与死神搏斗的总统
Attack a president who's fighting for his life?
叫你们来开会不是来辩论的
I didn't call this meeting to debate.
我要夺回那些州
I want those states back.
我们开始准备活动和媒体造势
So let's start organizing events and media hits.
明早之前  确定初步预算和安排
Prelim budgets and schedules, by tomorrow morning.
对于古德温的动机  人们有多种猜测
There has been much speculation as to Goodwin's motivations.
辛西娅
Cynthia.
古德温的事进展如何
Where are we on Goodwin?
已经搞定了保安
The security guy's taken care of.
他没看见你们在一起
He never saw the two of you together.
那其他人呢
What about others?
据他所知  没有
None that he knows of.
但我们又不能四处询问
But it's not like we can ask around.
在2013年11月
In November of 2013,
巴恩斯女士被华府地铁撞击身亡
Ms. Barnes was struck by a D.C. metrorail train.
枪手确认是卢卡斯·古德温
华府警方将其定性为一场事故
D.C. police classified it as an accident.
有人推测...
Some have speculated that...
坐吧  雷米
Have a seat, Remy.
弗兰克的事我很遗憾
Sorry about Frank.
拜托  省省吧
Oh, please, don't bother.
我已经听够了人们说他们很遗憾
I've had enough people say they're sorry,
我也知道你不是真心的
and I know you don't mean it.
我没办法按你希望的那样帮你
I can't help you the way you want me to.
莉安告诉我她已经跟你说得很明白了
LeAnn told me she was very clear with you.
没用的
It won't work.
塔斯克比我更不想帮你
Tusk wants to help you even less than I do.
这不是谁在帮谁  雷米
Well, nobody's doing any favors here, Remy.
他会从中获得一大笔钱
He's going to get very rich from this.
你为什么不亲自跟他说
Why don't you speak to him yourself?
因为他不会听我的
Because he won't listen to me.
这必须听起来像是你的主意  而不是我的
This needs to seem like your idea, not mine.
你也会捞上一大笔的
And you'll make a killing, too.
我不需要钱
I don't need the money.
因为你现在在乎的是别的
Because you care about other things now.
比如杰姬
Like Jackie.
所以你必须做成此事
Which is why you'll make this happen.
如果我当初跟邓巴说了弗兰克的事
If I had told Dunbar about Frank...
说他知道洗钱的事
about how he knew about the laundering,
他就当不了总统  我们现在也不会站在这儿
he wouldn't be president and we wouldn't be standing here.
但你没有  你现在也说不了了
But you didn't and you can't now,
所以现在是这样
so here we are.
两小时  我们毫无进展
Two hours and we got nowhere.
他只想听中国的反映
All he wants to hear is China.
我告诉他北京方面不回应
I told him Beijing is not responsive.
他根本不在乎
He doesn't give a damn.
第一夫人给他提过醒了
The First Lady put a bug in his ear.
不管她说了什么  他铁了心不听我们的了
Well, whatever bug she put in there won't crawl out.
我会安排次会面  只有你我他三人
I'll set up a meeting. Just you, me and him.
恐怕一次会面是不够的
I don't think a meeting is enough.
我们的副总统
We have a vice president
不知道他在干什么  道格
that does not know what he is doing, Doug.
他必须把外交事务
He needs to completely turn over
全部转交给国务院
all diplomatic affairs to the State Department.
-否则我完全无能为力  -现在不行
- Otherwise, my hands are tied. - Not now.
非常紧急
This can't wait.
我们结束后  我会去找你的
When we're finished, I will come and find you.
您能让我们单独谈谈吗  国务卿女士
Could you give us a few moments, Madam Secretary?
-赛斯  你太过分了  -没关系
- Seth, you're out of line! - It's all right.
给我打电话
Call me.
我会的  谢谢  凯茜
I will. Thank you, Cathy.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你他妈在干什么  -你不能开除我
- What the fuck are you doing? - You can't fire me.
你不能打断我和国务卿的会面
You don't interrupt a meeting with the Secretary of State.
我可以终结邓巴的竞选
I can end Dunbar's campaign.
今天就结束掉
We can end it today.
怎么做
How?
如果我做到  你能让我留下吗
If I deliver, will you keep me on?
你得先告诉我
You tell me how first.
坐吧  玛莎
Have a seat, Martha.
我重新考虑了一下你的辞职
I've had second thoughts about your resignation.
你还想继续当司法部长吗
Would you like to remain as attorney general?
是的  我想
Yes, I would.
谢谢  道格
Thank you, Doug.
希瑟·邓巴有没有告诉过你
Did Heather Dunbar inform you
她和卢卡斯·古德温见过面
of a meeting between herself and Lucas Goodwin?
你要让我的下属审问我吗
You're having me interrogated by my own subordinates?
你能保住工作  他们才是你的属下
They only work for you if you keep your job.
我建议你回答他们的问题
I suggest you answer their questions.
我想要我的律师在场
I'd like a lawyer present.
我提醒你  女士
Let me remind you, ma'am.
没告知我们已经构成了隐瞒证据
Failing to have informed us constitutes withholding of evidence.
希瑟是我的朋友
Heather is a friend.
非常简单  玛莎
It's very simple, Martha.
跟我们合作  你就继续当司法部长
You work with us, you stay on as AG.
不合作  我们就起诉
You don't, we prosecute.
女士们先生们  美国第一夫人
Ladies and Gentlemen, the First Lady of the United States.
大家下午好
Good afternoon, everyone.
我想向大家通报我丈夫康复的最新情况
I'd like to update you on my husband's recovery.
总统的医疗团队
The President's medical team
昨晚做出了全面的评估
gave me a full assessment last night
他们最后的结论是
and they have come to the conclusion
总统需要肝移植
that the President is in need of a liver transplant
才能活下去
if he's to survive.
我请求全国与我共同祈祷
I'm asking the nation to pray with me
弗朗西斯能尽快等到一个健康的肝脏
that a healthy liver makes its way to Francis soon.
抱歉  请等一下
I'm sorry. A moment.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
她很厉害  对吧
She's good, isn't she?
你在这儿干什么
What're you doing here?
至于案件调查...
As for the investigation...
第一夫人需要支持
First Lady wanted some support.
...联调局反恐处处长
...the FBI director of counterterrorism
会向大家进行全面汇报  但是...
will give you a full briefing. But...
我认为有必要亲自澄清
I feel it's important to personally address
在古德温先生住所找到的文件
the document found in Mr. Goodwin's residence
本次发布会前刚刚发到大家手上
that was made available to you just before this conference.
很多措辞足以成为引人注目的头条新闻
It's filled with language that would make for flashy headlines,
比如谋杀  腐败
words like "murder," "corruption."
他杀害了佐伊·巴恩斯和彼得·罗素
其中指控总统与彼得·罗素和
The accusation that the President was involved in the deaths
佐伊·巴恩斯的死有关
of Peter Russo and Zoe Barnes.
第一夫人发表全国讲话  古德温指安德伍德犯下谋杀
还有"滥用职权"这样的字眼
Phrases like "abuse of power,"
尽管这一切没有事实依据
while they have no basis in reality,
却让我们悲哀地一窥他饱受困扰的内心
they do give us a sad glimpse into a very troubled mind.
如果有人
And it pains me that anyone,
即使是有精神疾病的人
even someone who is mentally ill,
真会相信古德温先生对我丈夫的指控
would think my husband is capable of
那会让我十分痛心
what Mr.Goodwin believed to be true.
但最让我心痛的是古德温先生的父母
But mostly it pains me for Mr. Goodwin's parents,
他们还在应对失去儿子的痛苦
who are coping with the loss of their son.
据大家说  他一生中大部分时候是个好人
And, by all accounts, he was a decent man for most of his life,
但显然  他内心的什么地方崩溃了
but clearly, something snapped in him
而他迫切需要的时候没能得到帮助
and he never got the help he so desperately needed.
所以我恳请大家尊重他的父母
So I ask that all of you respect his parents' grief
不要对这个生病的年轻人的话加以渲染
by not sensationalizing the words of a sick young man.
让我们记住劳伦斯和贝蒂·密查姆
And let's remember Lawrence and Betty Meechum,
他们的儿子艾德华
whose son Edward
因为古德温先生的病献出了自己的生命
gave his life because of Mr. Goodwin's illness.
艾德华的牺牲是我丈夫还活着的唯一原因
Edward's sacrifice is the only reason my husband is still alive.
我会永远感激
And I'll be forever grateful
他的友谊和奉献
for his friendship and his devoted service.
谢谢
Thank you.
反恐处处长纳森·格林
Counterterrorism Director Nathan Green.
今天调查取得了新进展
Today we had a new development in the investigation.
今天下午我们采访了司法部长
This afternoon, we interviewed the Attorney General.
她告诉了我们她和希瑟·邓巴
She gave us a full account of a conversation she had
在枪击当天进行的谈话的全部内容
with Heather Dunbar the day of the shooting.
谈话中  邓巴女士声称
In this conversation, Ms. Dunbar claimed to have met
曾亲自见过卢卡斯·古德温
with Lucas Goodwin personally.
我们虽没有理由相信
And while we have no reason to believe
邓巴女士和刺杀企图有任何关系
Ms. Dunbar had anything to do with the assassination attempt...
我们会对她就这个宣称的谈话进行质询
we will be questioning her about this alleged conversation.
你们要抓她吗
Are you arresting her?
不  女士  我们只是来问几个问题
No, ma'am. We're here to ask a few questions.
-那你需要提交正式申请  -她现在在吗
- Then you need to make a formal request. - Is she here now?
直接把申请发给我
Send the request directly to me,
我会和邓巴女士的律师讨论
and then I'll discuss it with Ms. Dunbar's attorneys.
凯特
Hey, Kate.
我给你打过电话  固话和手机
I tried calling. Home and cell.
座机线拔了  手机关机了
Pulled out the cord. Turned off the cell.
因为我这种人
Because of people like me.
其他人至少有礼貌没跑来我家门口
The others had the courtesy not to show up on my doorstep.
礼貌从没帮我达成什么目的
Courtesy never got me anywhere.
我们能谈谈吗  私下谈
Can we talk? Off the record.
要不是你的话...
If it were anyone but you...
幸运的是  是我
Well, luckily, it isn't.
我去牵福斯托  该遛他了
Let me get Fausto. It's time for his walk.
我是核行业的  不是化石燃料
I'm in the nuclear game, not fossil fuels.
没人有你在中国那样的关系
No one has the relationships you do in China.
中国人已经跟我脱离关系了
Chinese disowned me.
他们会回心转意的
They'll come around.
谁让你来的
Who put you up to this?
我要开自己的公司
Starting my own firm.
我以为你不干了
I thought you were out?
我那是在自欺欺人
I was fooling myself.
总统刚被枪击
So, president gets shot,
你就忍不住要趁火打劫了
and you just can't help taking advantage of the chaos.
你所说的火  我称之为机遇
What you call chaos, I call opportunity.
你是我的第一位客户
And you're my first client.
祝你好运
I wish you the best.
但我不是你的第一位客户
But I'm not your first client.
我不想跟白宫扯上关系
I don't wanna have anything to do with the White House.
你因为沃克的丑闻损失了很多钱
You lost a lot of money during the Walker scandal.
没错  正因此我才要拒绝你
I did, indeed, which is why I'm turning you down.
我很抱歉你跑了这么大老远结果被拒绝
I'm sorry you came all the way out here for a "No."
你不想进监狱吧
You don't wanna go to prison, do you?
再失去仅剩的一切
Lose the rest of it?
我已经被赦免了
I've already been pardoned.
免的是洗钱罪  不是伪证罪
For the money laundering, not for perjury.
你说沃克知道  但是他不知道
You said that Walker knew, and he didn't.
你没有说你当时是跟弗兰克合作
What you didn't say is that you were working with Frank.
人家凭什么相信你而不是我
Why should anybody believe you more than me?
你要么赌一把
You take that chance...
然后看着克雷顿-维斯特变成低价股
and watch Clayton West become a penny stock.
要么我们成为终结石油危机的英雄
Or we're heroes for ending the oil crisis,
大家都发财  你也能重树形象
everybody gets rich, your image is restored.
他们也许还会让你选
They'll probably even let you choose
下一任驻北京的大使
the next ambassador in Beijing.
你不觉得那是真的吗
So you don't think any of it is true?
不
No.
我想相信他
And I wanted to believe him.
那第一夫人泪眼汪汪说的那些话
So the First Lady's whole teary-eyed thing?
我觉得她是对的
I think she's right.
卢卡斯是哪里崩溃了吧
Something in Lucas snapped.
我认识的卢卡斯不会想杀死总统
I mean, the Lucas I knew wouldn't have tried to kill a president.
没错  我就是这意思
Exactly. That's my point.
你真觉得安德伍德杀过人吗
You honestly think Underwood was murdering people?
你的怀疑态度哪去了
Where is your skepticism?
我怀疑卢卡斯  也怀疑白宫
I'm skeptical of Lucas and I'm skeptical of the White House.
那怎么没证据
How come there's no proof?
没有
None.
卢卡斯试了  我也试了
After Lucas tried, after I tried.
我的建议是算了吧
My advice is to let it go.
你只会重复我们的徒劳
You're gonna repeat the same goose chase we did.
我总得问一下
I had to ask.
-你的编辑说了什么  -说算了吧
- What does your editor say? - To let it go.
你看吧
You see?
-他可不如你  -那是我以前
- He's not as good as you are. - Was.
真希望你在《电讯报》工作
Wish you were at The Telegraph.
是啊  要是有人被开了就告诉我
Yeah, let me know if anyone gets fired.
活体捐献者常见问题
门没关
It's open.
我一收到你的短信就尽快赶过来了
I came as soon as I got your text.
发布会后我们忙得不可开交
We've been slammed since the press conference.
情况怎么样
How's it lookin'?
邓巴的事大受关注
Major play on the Dunbar story.
让第一夫人去说是个好主意
It was a good idea to have the First Lady talk.
你要喝苏打水吗
You want a soda?
来杯水什么的吗
A glass of water or anything?
水就好
Water's fine.
我已决定让你留下来了
I've decided you can stay.
道格  我希望你能理解
Doug, I hope you can understand.
我紧张了
I got nervous.
当时情况看起来不太好
You know, things weren't looking good and...
我想留条退路  以防万一
yeah, I wanted an out, in case I needed one.
那的确是个错误  我希望我没有那样做
I mean, it was a mistake. I wish I hadn't.
你纠正了你的错误
You corrected your mistakes.
那才是最重要的  要冰块吗
That's all that matters. You want ice?
好的
Sure.
我们现在不能让竞选再出现问题了
We can't afford any more shake-ups in the campaign right now,
尤其总统还在医院里
especially with the president in the hospital.
我们也不能让你再犯错
We also can't afford any more of your mistakes.
闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up. Shut up!
我刚醒来的时候  说不出话
When I first woke up, I couldn't speak.
我得眨眼来表达我的反应
I had to blink my eyes if I wanted to respond.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
如果我得不到你的忠诚
If I can't get your loyalty,
那我就要你顺从
I will have your obedience.
眨眼
Blink.
Blink!
该死
Fuck!
该死的
Fucking...
给
Here.
你有病  伙计
You're fucked up, man.
-别叫了  -早上好  汉默施密特先生
- Quit it. - Good morning, Mr. Hammerschmidt.
有什么事吗
How can I help you?
我们来还你的笔记
Uh, we're just returning your notes.
我们复印过了  这是原件
We made copies. These are the originals.
不是很有用吧
Nothing too useful, huh?
是的  先生  但还是感谢你的配合
No, sir, but thank you for your cooperation.
还有你的报纸  放在台阶上的
Your paper, too. It was on the step.
祝你今天愉快  汉默施密特先生
Well, you have a good day, Mr. Hammerschmidt.
你们也是
You, too.
不要告诉我你又饿了
Don't tell me you're hungry already.
我才喂过你  天呐
I just fed you. Good God.
来了  来了  来了  来了
I'm coming. I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
未遂刺客说法被驳斥
邓巴未对古德温一事做出回应
-早上好  -早上好
- Morning. - Morning.
我建议让凯茜来做谈判
I suggest we turn the negotiations over to Cathy.
如果我们一直拖着俄国  油价会
If we keep stalling on Russia, gas prices will--
现在不是说这个的时候
Now is not a good time.
我不会让总统
I won't have the president
回到一个一片混乱的白宫
come back to a White House in disarray.
我们不知道他会不会回来
We don't know that he is coming back.
他会的  我向你保证
He is. I promise you that.
你是上帝吗  你有什么资格保证
Are you God? Who are you to say?
什么事
Yes?
塔斯克先生和丹顿先生来了
Mr. Tusk and Mr. Danton are here.
让他们进来
Send them in.
今早安排的  我们要讨论俄国的事
It was arranged this morning. We're discussing Russia.
先生  我是幕僚长
Sir, I am the Chief of Staff.
这些事情你必须让我知道
You have to keep me informed of these things.
不好意思
Excuse me,
但我觉得应该是你要听我的
but I believe you answer to me,
而不是反过来
not the other way around.
国务卿杜兰特应该参加这个会
Secretary Durant should be here.
这是一次私下碰面
This meeting is private.
我之后会跟你们俩讨论
I'll discuss it with you both after.
总统绝不会允许雷蒙德
The president would never allow Raymond--
-总统先生  -塔斯克先生
- Mr. President. - Mr. Tusk.
雷米  很高兴见到你
Remy, good to see you.
-总统先生  -斯坦普先生
- Mr. President. - Mr. Stamper.
我们稍后继续  道格
I'll follow up with you later, Doug.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
感谢您这么快就抽出时间见我们
Thanks for taking the time to meet with us on such short notice.
石油的问题没时间可以浪费了
Well, there's no time to waste on this oil thing.
我跟中国那边有了些进展
I've made some progress with the Chinese.
先生  第一夫人现在在里面
Sir, the First Lady is in there right now.
她在等我
She's expecting me.
我们还想赢得选举呢
We're trying to win an election,
你却想提醒所有人
and you want to remind everyone
总统赦免了雷蒙德·塔斯克
that the president pardoned Raymond Tusk?
我们换个地方说
Let's find somewhere else.
这都是国家大事
These are matters of state.
你无权干涉
You don't have the authority to intervene.
如果唐纳德想听我的建议  那他就有权这么做
If Donald wants my counsel, that is his prerogative.
你故意骗我
You are deliberately deceiving me.
-你背着我  -你忘了你的身份  道格拉斯
- Going behind my-- - You have forgotten your place, Douglas.
我的身份  那你呢
My place? What about your place?
你在他最需要的时候离开  还威胁他
You leave him when he needs you most, you threaten him,
现在他进了医院  你还拆他的台
and now that he's in here, you undermine him.
-你应该  -别说了  够了
- You're supposed to be-- - Stop. That is enough.
我会告诉你一切
I will fill you in on everything,
但不是在这儿  而是在白宫
but not here. At the White House.
怎么了
What's happening?
他的心脏
His heart.
-医生  -他有些偶发心律不齐
- Doctor? - He's had some sporadic arrhythmia.
-请出去一下好吗  -好
- Will you give us the room for a moment? - Of course.
我们不能一直斗下去
We can't keep battling each other,
他都这样子了
not with him like this.
我们需要一条新的道路
We need a new path forward,
我希望你能帮忙
and I would like your help with that.
我保证不会瞒着你
I promise I won't keep you in the dark.
等你准备好  我们白宫见
I'll meet you at the White House whenever you're ready.
我要留在这里  我觉得这更重要
I'm staying here. I think this is more important.
好
Okay.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood.
关于如何对付俄国
Mr. Tusk and Mr. Danton have a proposal
塔斯克先生和丹顿先生有个提议
about how to deal with Russia.
您今天最没想到会见到的就是我吧
I imagine I'm the last person you expected to see today.
见到你们二位
I am a bit surprised,
我的确有些惊讶
yes, to see both of you.
大家对我们的到来肯定都有些警觉
I'm sure there's some wariness about us being here,
但我们有个对付俄国的好计划
but I think we have a good plan on how to handle Russia.
你想加入吗
Would you like to join us?
让雷蒙德给你详说
Raymond can lay it out for you.
我不知道我能提供些什么
Well, I don't know what I can offer.
要是我又跟白宫打交道的消息传出去
Well, we're going to catch some flack if word gets out
我们会受到抨击的
that I'm back in business with the White House.
你可以帮我们平息那些声音
You could help us smooth that over.
你的新闻发布会相当感人
Your press conference was very moving.
-弗兰克的事  我很遗憾  -谢谢
- I'm sorry about Frank. - Thank you.
当然  他要是知道我进了总统办公室
Of course, he'd have a conniption fit
肯定会大发脾气
if he knew I were in the Oval Office.
他是个实用主义者  雷蒙德  只要成功就行
Well, he is a pragmatist, Raymond. Whatever works.
-我们继续吧  -雷米
- Shall we continue? - Remy.
计划是向中美能源公司提出
So, the plan is to propose a partnership
建立伙伴关系
between American and Chinese energy companies.
你有点紧张
You seem nervous.
有一阵子没见了
It's been a while.
我该怎么办  老大
What should I do, boss?
萨克逊医生
Dr. Saxon.
我想捐肝
I'd like to donate.
-斯坦普先生  -我是O型血
- Mr. Stamper-- - My blood type is O.
我很健康  我们开始做测试吧
I'm healthy. Let's do the tests.
健康不是捐肝的唯一标准
That's not the only criteria for donation.
你是个正在戒酒的酗酒者  我们不接受
You're a recovering alcoholic. We don't accept--
我不管什么规则
I don't care about the rules.
如果我配型成功  我希望你能做
If I'm a match, I want you to do it.
就算成功了  也帮不上忙
Even if you were, it wouldn't matter.
他已经病得太重  只有部分肝脏不够
He's too ill for a partial liver at this point.
他需要一整个
He needs a full one.
抱歉  但我们只能等待并企盼了
I'm sorry, but we'll just have to wait and hope.